Guide to the Gathering of the Tribes Archive 1983-2006 MSS.198
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Media
  - Subseries A: Video
    - The Descendants of Africa, June 14 2001; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 00:09:05; Commercial Release (W.E.T. Productions).; Original Format: VHS (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0213)
    - A Gathering of the Tribes Tenth Anniversary Celebration on the Occasion of The Charlie Parker Festival, August 29 2001; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0116)
    - L'Humor i la Rabia, 2001; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0015)
    - New Yorkers: Steve Cannon, October 20 2002; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Commercial / promotional release (Berko Productions).; Original Format: VHS (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0196)
    - New Yorkers: Steve Cannon, October 20 2002; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Commercial / promotional release (Berko Productions).; Original Format: VHS (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0198)
    - New Yorkers: Steve Cannon - Outtakes, [October 20 2002]; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Commercial / promotional release (Berko Productions).; Original Format: VHS (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0299)
    - Chinese Musicians, November 2002; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 5, Cassette ID: 198.0165)
    - The Jerome Reading Series Presents: Christina Chiu & Lourdes Vazquez with musical interludes by Ji Hong, at Tribes, December 1 2002; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "funded in part by the Jerome Foundation"; "by Susan L. Yung"; Original Format: VHS (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0132)
    - Iberian Tribes, December 6 2002; 1 media elements Total Running Time: approx. 01:00:00; Label annotation: "Susan L. Yung"; Original Format: VHS (Box 4, Cassette ID: 198.0133)
    - Alcatraz is Not an Island, 2002; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 00:56:40; Commercial Release (ITVS).; Original Format: VHS (Box 2, Cassette ID: 198.0048)
    - Mighty Times: The Legacy of Rosa Parks, 2002; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 00:40:00; Original Format: VHS; Commercial release (Southern Poverty Law Center). (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0267)
    - Mighty Times: The Legacy of Rosa Parks, 2002; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 00:40:00; Original Format: VHS; Commercial Release (Southern Poverty Law Center). (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0268)
    - N9: A DVD Magazine (Volume 2), 2002; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: DVD; Commercial Release. (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0242)
    - N9: A DVD Magazine (Volume 2), 2002; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: DVD; Commercial Release. (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0243)
    - N9: A DVD Magazine (Volume 2), 2002; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: DVD; Commercial release. (Box 9, Disk ID: 198.0317)
    - N9: A DVD Magazine (Volume 2), 2002; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: DVD; Commercial release. (Box 9, Disk ID: 198.0318)
    - Poetry Show: Billy Bang, January 2003; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0237)
    - Poetry Show: Steve [Del...] & Yuko [Oto..] / Billy [Bang], January 2003; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS.; Label inside cassette sleeve torn in half. (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0236)
    - Tribes 1) 2/16/03 2) Charles Wright 3/2/03 "The Wig" BK party, February - March 2003; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "by Susan L. Yung".; Original Format: VHS (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0224)
    - Tribes 3-14-03 - Closing Party / 3-16-03 - Poetry Reading - Anyssa Kim, Wang Pang & Kamiko Hahn (No Show), March 14 & 16 2003; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "by Susan L. Yung".; Original Format: VHS (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0208)
    - Tribes Art Opening @ Indian Music & 'Voices'; Artists: Bridget Galway, Kara Williamson, March 21 2003; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0211)
    - Tribes @ Sarah Lawrence 4-11-03 / Tribes @ Bowery Poetry Club 4-21-03 / Unbearables @ Tribes 5-2-03, April - May 2003; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0241)
    - Tribes @ Nuyorican Poets Cafe - w/ Anyssa Kim, Vong, Lourdes Vargas, May 14 2003; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0239)
    - Carl Hancock Rux @ Visions Festival, May 21 2003; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "by Susan L. Yung".; Original Format: VHS (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0222)
    - Tribes @ Cornelia St. Cafe: Dawoud on Sitar; Poets - Anyssa Kim & Nadine Mozon, June 4 2003; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0256)
    - Tribes - Pedro Pietri, Onome Djere & Tom Savage / The Reggie Nicholson Trio w/ Kalaparush McIntyer, Brian Smith, July 6 2003; 1 media elements Total Running Tiem: Unknown; Original Format: VHS; Label annotation: "by Susan L. Yung". (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0260)
      Flyer removed from original cassette sleeve and housed in series.
    - Oops, July 12 2003; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0246)
    - Tribes @ Blue Stockings Bookstore: "Oops" by Steve Cannon; Barbara Purcell; & Anyssa Kim, July 15 2003; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0206)
    - Free Tibet @ Tribes, July 27 2003; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS; Label annotation: "by Susan L. Yung". (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0258)
    - Oops; Mia Kim's "Fashion Madness" & [J]ong @ Tribes, August 7 2003; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0221)
    - Tribes @ Nuyorican Poets Cafe with Anyssa Kim & Blackout @ Grand Army Plaza, August 13 2003; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0201)
    - Yuko Fujimama Trio w/ Roy Campbell & Reggie Nicholson @ Tribes, August 17 2003; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS; Label annotation: "by Susan L. Yung" (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0238)
    - Jazzmobile with Hilton Ruiz @ Tribes, August 25 2003; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "by Susan L. Yung".; Original Format: VHS (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0202)
    - Charlie Parker Exhibit @ Tribes, August 29 2003; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0226)
    - Chors of Poets, conducted by Butch Morris, bowery Poetry Club, September 2003; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0220)
    - Anyssa Kim Book Party @ Bowery Poetry Club, October 2003; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0214)
    - Howl, December 17 2003; 1 media elements Total Running Time: approx. 00:10:00; Original Format: VHS. (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0244)
    - Wynton Marsalis: Up Close and Personal, 2003; 1 media elements Total Running Time: approx. 01:00:00; Original Format: VHS (Box 1, Cassette ID: 198.0007)
    - 12-11-03 - Brian Leo @ Tribes / 1-23-04 Michael Tong's Tea Party @ Tribes (Chinese New Year), circa 1990-2007; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS; Label annotation: "by Susan L. Yung". (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0265)
    - Gulsen Calik @ Tribes - Closing / Lois Elaine Griffith @ Tribes about Pedro Pietri, March 7 2004; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "by Susan L. Yung".; Original Format: VHS (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0200)
    - El Negro Mas Chulo: African by Legacy, Mexican by Birth - Ayana v. Jackson & Marco Villalobos, April 10 2004; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "by Susan L. Yung".; Original Format: VHS (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0215)
    - 5-2-04 - Huang Xiang @ Tribes / 5-6-04 - Yusef Komunyakaa & Wang Ping @ Tribes, May 2 & 6 2004; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS; Label annotation: "by Susan L. Yung" (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0257)
    - ChrisTwomey, Art and Genetics in a Digital Age - Artists Talk on Art - PANEL DISCUSSION, May 21 2004; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0274)
    - Jazz Mobile @ Tribes w/ Ed Vega, May 22 2004; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS; Label annotation: "By Susan L. Yung". (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0269)
    - Vision Festival 9 - NY Skyscraper, conducted by Butch Morris, May 31 2004; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Label annotation: "video by Susan L. Yung".; Original Format: VHS (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0203)
    - ChrisTwomey, OMNI SERIES - Art and Genetics in a Digital Age - CNN, Jeanne Moos, June 3 2004; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 00:01:30; Original Format: VHS (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0279)
    - 7-9-04 Sabir Mateen & Susan L. Yung @ 128 Rivington Gallery / 6-19-04 - Dor Green @ Tribes "William", June - July 2004; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS; Label annotation: "by Susan L. Yung" (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0263)
    - First Queens International Poetry Festival, 2004; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0280)
    - 2-12-05 - Tribes - John Ranard & Chin Chin Yang / 2-19-05 - Evie Ivy's "Dance of the Word", February 12 & 19 2005; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS; Label annotation: "by Susan L. Yung" (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0292)
    - Butch Morris conducts: A Chorus of Poets, at Nuyorican Poets Cafe, June 28 2005; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS; Label annotation: "by Susan L. Yung". (Box 8, Cassette ID: 198.0293)
    - The Newshour with Jim Lehrer, April 10 2006; 1 media elements Total Running Time: Unknown; Original Format: VHS; Contains a segment entitled "Stormy Words", about poetry in New Orleans. (Box 9, Cassette ID: 198.0320)
      A request letter for a copy of the episode, addressed to "Strictly 4 Business", was removed from the original cassette case to Series III. It can be found in Box 17, Folder 20.
  - Subseries B: Audio
    - Ambush at Fort Bragg, by Tom Wolfe, 1997; ID: 198.0062; 4 media elements 4 audiocassettes Total Running Time: approx. 03:00:00; Commercial audiobook release, performed by Edward Norton (Bantam Doubleday Dell Audio Publishing). (Box 2, Media ID: 198.0062)
    - At Home in the World: A Memoir, by Joyce Maynard, 1998; ID: 198.0284; 2 media elements 2 audiocassettes; Total Running Time: Unknown; Oiginal Format: Audiocassette; Commercial release (Soundelux Audio Publishing). (Box 8, Media ID: 198.0284)
    - Blood Work, by Michael Connelly, 1998; ID: 198.0285; 5 media elements 5 audiocassettes Total Running Time: approx. 15:00:00; Original Format: Audiocassettes (Box 8, Media ID: 198.0285)
    - The Inferno, of Dante, 1998; ID: 198.0295; 4 media elements Total Running Time: approx. 06:00:00; Original Format: Audiocassette (Box 8, Media ID: 198.0295)
    - Jazz, by Toni Morrison, 1992; ID: 198.0161; 2 media elements 2 audiocassettes Total Running Time:; Commercial Release (Random House Audiobooks). (Box 5, Media ID: 198.0161)
    - Little Evil Things, 1997; 1 media elements Total Running Time: 00:56:00; Commercial release (Penton Overseas, Inc.). (Box 7, Cassette ID: 198.0230)
    - Mrs. Ted Bliss, by Stanley Elkin, 1997; ID: 198.0145; 9 media elements 9 audiocassettes Total Running Time: 12:45:00; Commercial release (Recorded Books, Inc.). (Box 4, Media ID: 198.0145)
    - The Poet, by Michael Connelly, 1996; ID: 198.0216; 5 media elements 5 audiocassettes Total Running Time: approx. 15:00:00 (Box 6, Media ID: 198.0216)
    - The Tao Te Ching, 1997; 1 media elements 1 audiocassette Total Running Time: 01:20:00; Commercial audiobook release, read by Nigel Hawthorne (Mystic Fire Audio). (Box 6, Cassette ID: 198.0212)
- Series II: Scrapbooks
  This series contains scrapbooks maintained by the Gathering of the Tribes staff, documenting events and publications. Each scrapbook holds an arrangement of photographs, ephemera, and clippings related to the gallery and magazine.
  Materials from each scrapbook were rehoused, in their original order, into archival storage binders.
  - Scrapbook, 1992-1994 (Box 23, Binder 10)
  - Scrapbook, 1992-2001 (Box 23, Binder 10)
  - Scrapbook, 1993-1994 (Box 23, Binder 10)
  - Scrapbook, 1996-1999 (Box 23, Binder 11)
  - Scrapbook, 1996 (Box 23, Binder 11)
  - Scrapbook, 1996 (Box 23, Binder 11)
  - Scrapbook, 1997 (Box 23, Binder 12)
  - Scrapbook, 1995-1998 (Box 23, Binder 12)
  - Scrapbook, 1998 (Box 23, Binder 13)
  - Scrapbook (1 of 2), 1999 (Box 23, Binder 13)
  - Scrapbook (2 of 2), 1999 (Box 24, Binder 14)
  - Scrapbook, 1999-2000 (Box 24, Binder 14)
  - Scrapbook, 1999-2001 (Box 24, Binder 15)
  - Scrapbook, 2000-2001 (Box 24, Binder 15)
  - Scrapbook, 2001-2002 (Box 24, Binder 16)
- Series III: Project Files
  Materials are arranged alphabetically by file title.
  - America Too, by LaVerne Williams, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Articles, 1995-2002 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Articles, 1999-2000 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Axel, Bret, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Barnum and Buddha's Poetry Circus, March 2001 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Beatty, Paul, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Benson, Tish, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Bishara, Rana, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Blackburn, Bob, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Bloom, Randy, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Bradley, Peter, 2001-2003 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Calendars and Press Releases, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Charles Gayle Gala, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Charlie Parker Festival, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Charlie Parker Festival, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Chiang, Fay, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Chromatic Cryptology Art Show, March 2001 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Clarke, Kevin, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Coppola, John, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1999-2006 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 2005-2007 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Cruz, Victor Hernandez, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Equinox: Collected Poems, by Barbara Chase-Riboud, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - (E)tres, circa 2001 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Espinoza, Dora, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Events, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Events, March - August 2002 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Events, September - December 2002 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Feuer, Ejlat, 1998-2002 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Flyers and Postcards, 1997-2003 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Forester, Victoria, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Galleri Uten Navn, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Gallery Files (1 of 3), 2001 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Gallery Files (2 of 3), 2001 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Gallery Files (3 of 3), 2001 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - A Gathering of the Tribes, Issue #6 Galleys, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - A Gathering of the Tribes, Issue #9 Galleys, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - A Gathering of the Tribes Press Package, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Gaze, Tim, 2000-2002 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Get Off That Alligator!, by Martin Marriott, undated (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Gissen, Linda, 1987-1996 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Goddess City, 1997, undated (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Gohl, Andrea, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Hammons, David, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Hoagland, Everett, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - "Iberian Tribes" Catalog, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    File contains an audio CD; please request to use Fales equipment for playback.
  - Inez, Colette, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Johnson, Nikki, circa 2002 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Kent, Lori, undated (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Kim, Anyssa, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Kim, Anyssa, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Kim, Anyssa, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Kim, Anyssa, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - The Long Decade: Mor Faye and Ba Rah, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    File contains audio CD; please request Fales equipment for playback.
  - Lorenzo Pace Sculpture Unveiling, circa 1983-2006 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Photos removed from VHS ID 198.0209 cassette sleeve.
  - Marsalis, Wynton, 2002-2003 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Montford, Dan Loudfoot, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Myles, Eileen, 2001-2002 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Neumann, Shalom, 2002-2003 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - New York and African Tapestries, by Juanita Torrence-Thompson, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Olinka, Sharon, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Ovarian Twists, by Anyssa Kim, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Packer, Eve, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Poetry Contest, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Poets Info, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Prison Poster Project, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Rabinsky, Deborah, 1992-2000 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Radosavljevic, Dunja, undated (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Ranard, John, 1997-2002 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Reed, Ishmael, 2002-2003 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Resumes, circa 2000-2007 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Reyes, Aileen, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Sentis, Mireia, 1998-2002 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Shows, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Simmons, Daniel, circa 1996 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Smith, Ming, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Submissions, 1998-2003 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Submissions, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Submissions, 1999-2004 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Submissions, 2000-2002 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Submissions, 2000-2002 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Submissions, 2000-2003 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Submissions, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Submissions, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Submissions, 2001-2002 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Submissions - For Next Issue, 2000-2001 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Submissions - Maybe, 2001-2002 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Submissions - Rejected, undated (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Submissions - Yes, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Submissions - A Gathering of the Tribes Issue #9, 2002-2003 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Submissions, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Subscriptions, 2000-2002 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Tong, Michael, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Tribes Art Collection, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Tribes Gallery Flyers, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Twomey, Chris, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Van Dyne, Wolfgang, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Villalobos, Marco, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Wakili, Shekaiba, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Watanabe, Tadashi, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - "Who is the Powerful Ghost", May 6-27 2000 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Yung, Susan, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 48)
- Series IV: Grant Applications
  - The Andy Warhol Foundation, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - The Andy Warhol Foundation, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Chase Manhattan Bank, 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Department of Cultural Affairs, 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Department of Cultural Affairs, 1998-2002 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Department of Cultural Affairs, 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Department of Cultural Affairs Challenge, Fiscal Year 01, 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Department of Cultural Affairs, February 2001 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Department of Cultural Affairs, May 2001 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Department of Cultural Affairs, Fiscal year 02, 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Department of Cultural Affairs, 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Ford Foundation, 1995-2001 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Foundation for Contemporary Performance Arts, 1999-2001 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Foundation for Contemporary Performance Arts, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Fund for the City of New York, 1996-1999 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Fund for the City of New York, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Fund for the City of New York, 2002-2003 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Funding, Acceptance, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Gannett Foundation, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Golden Rule Foundation, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Greenwall Foundation, 1995-1999 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Greenwall Foundation, 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - The Gunk Foundation, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Jerome Foundation, 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Jerome Foundation, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Jerome Foundation, Fiscal Year 00, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Jerome Foundation, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Jerome Foundation, Support & Materials, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Jerome Foundation, Letters of Support, 2000-2002 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Jerome Foundation, Fiscal Year 02, 2000-2003 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Jerome Foundation, Final Report 02, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Lannan Foundation, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - LEF Foundation, 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - LEF Foundation, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - LEF Foundation, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - LEF Foundation, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Lopez, Margarita, 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Manhattan Arts Development Fund, Fiscal year 01, 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Meet the Composer, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - New York Foundation for the Arts '00 Community Assets, 1998-2002 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - New York Foundation for the Arts - Tech Tap Fiscal Year '01, 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - New York State Council on the Arts Book Pub Request, 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - New York State Council on the Arts Magazine Request, 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - New York State Council on the Arts Final Reports, 1997-1999 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - New York State Council on the Arts - General, 1997-2000 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - New York State Council on the Arts Magazine Request, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - New York State Council on the Arts Website Request, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - New York State Council on the Arts Book Publishing Request, 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - New York State Council on the Arts TA Request, 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - New York State Council on the Arts Theater Request, 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - New York State Council on the Arts Writers in Residence, 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - New York State Council on the Arts Book Pub Request, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - New York State Council on the Arts E-Book Request, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - New York State Council on the Arts Magazine Request, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - New York State Council on the Arts Notes, 1999-2001 (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - New York State Council on the Arts TA Request, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - New York State Council on the Arts Tech Request, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - New York State Council on the Arts - Digital Tech Initiatives, Literary Publishing, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - New York State Council on the Arts Final Report Fiscal Year 01, 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - New York State Council on the Arts - Request and Grant Return, 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - New York State Council on the Arts Sup - Reading Series, Fiscal Year 02, 2000-2002 (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - New York State Council on the Arts, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 64)
  - New York State Council on the Arts - Grant, Fiscal Year '02, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 65)
  - New York State Council on the Arts - Contract, Final Report, Fiscal Year '02, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 66)
  - New York State Council on the Arts, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 67)
  - New York State Council on the Arts '01-'02 Blank Form, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 68)
  - New York State Council on the Arts - Final Report Literature, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 69)
  - Non-Profit Finance Fund, 2000-2002 (Box 19, Folder 70)